#### Contact

6158099215 (Mobile) coalpierce@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ashton-pierce (LinkedIn)

apierce17.github.io/react-portfolio-2021/ (Portfolio)

### Top Skills

React.js Adobe Photoshop CSS

# **Ashton Pierce**

Web Developer at SP+ (SP Plus) Shelbyville

# Summary

Full-stack web developer with nearly ten years of experience in graphic design. Skills in React.JS, CSS, and JavaScript and strengths in meeting deadlines, creativity, and communication. Continuously looking to overcome challenges in programming and working with others.

# Experience

SP+ (SP Plus)
Web Developer
February 2021 - Present (7 months)
Nashville, Tennessee, United States

- Build web pages for various company projects
- · Implement company technology into client sites
- Match new website design and feel to existing client sites
- Communicate with multiple teams to make sure targets and deadlines are met

#### V1 Tech

Graphic Designer May 2020 - May 2021 (1 year 1 month) United States

- · Prepare orders for production
- Use of Corel Draw and Photoshop
- Review customer instructions and implement them
- · Track completed orders
- Email customers upon request
- · Communicate with other designers efficiently

## Education

Vanderbilt University

Certification, Full Stack Web Development · (December 2020 - May 2021)